FOR THE SAKE OF LOVE
사랑을 위해
EPISODE 1
에피소드 1
Yu Ling.
유 링.
Do you need help?
도움이 필요하신가요?
No, thank you.
아니요 괜찮습니다.
Let me help you.
내가 도와 줄게.
So, I can say that I have been involved in a big interview.
그래서 큰 인터뷰에 참여하게 됐다고 할 수 있죠 .
I heard that Mrs. Yi highly recommended you.
이씨 부인이 당신을 적극 추천했다고 들었습니다 .
You're our magazine's flagship journalist.
당신은 우리 잡지의 대표 저널리스트입니다.
You have to do this interview.
이 인터뷰를 해야 합니다.
Yu Ling, the sales of the next issue will definitely skyrocket.
Yu Ling, 다음 호의 판매량은 확실히 급증할 것입니다.
Mrs. Yi has given me a very important task.
이씨 부인은 나에게 매우 중요한 임무를 맡겼다 .
I will try hard.
열심히 노력하겠습니다.
You lost the opportunity to interview Shi Yan.
당신은 Shi Yan과 인터뷰할 기회를 놓쳤습니다 .
Why are you still reviewing your interview draft, Zheng Shu Yi?
Zheng Shu Yi님, 왜 아직도 인터뷰 초안을 검토하고 계시나요 ?
Shi Yan might be an unusual guy.
Shi Yan은 특이한 사람일 수도 있습니다.
I'm just checking my draft again.
방금 초안을 다시 확인 중이에요.
Some questions are too conservative.
일부 질문은 너무 보수적입니다.
Obviously it can be improved.
분명히 개선될 수 있습니다.
I will perfect it.
나는 그것을 완벽하게 할 것이다.
Are you okay?
괜찮으세요?
Is missing an interview making you crazy?
인터뷰를 놓치면 미칠 것 같나요?
Even if you have a perfect draft,
완벽한 초안이 있어도
Shi Yan won't come back to you.
Shi Yan은 당신에게 돌아오지 않을 것입니다.
I heard that the Editor-in-Chief called Mingyu Yunchuang
편집장이 민규 윤추앙이라는 사람을 불렀다고 들었습니다.
and highly recommend the guy.
그리고 그 사람을 적극 추천합니다.
So, tactics are more important than competence.
그래서 실력보다는 전술이 더 중요합니다.
There are many important figures. Even though I lost Shi Yan,
중요한 인물이 많이 있습니다. 비록 시옌을 잃었지만
there are still other opportunities.
아직 다른 기회가 있습니다.
Having tactics can only get you one interview,
전술이 있으면 인터뷰는 한 번만 할 수 있습니다.
but competence can help you write good articles.
하지만 능력은 좋은 기사를 쓰는 데 도움이 될 수 있습니다.
Because I'm bad at tactics, I will continue to hone my competence.
제가 전술이 서툴기 때문에 계속해서 실력을 갈고닦아 나가겠습니다.
It's a pity that you can't help me see what Shi Yan looks like.
Shi Yan의 모습을 보도록 도와드릴 수 없다는 것이 안타깝습니다 .
Is he handsome or not?
그 사람은 잘생겼나요?
Mr. Shi, interview with Financial Introduction
Shi 씨, Financial Introduction 인터뷰
scheduled for 19.00 after dinner.
저녁 식사 후 19:00로 예정되어 있습니다 .
Journalist Xu Yu Ling will come to the office to interview you.
Xu Yu Ling 기자가 당신을 인터뷰하기 위해 사무실로 올 것입니다.
I don't think I'd choose Ms. Xu to interview me.
저는 Ms. Xu를 인터뷰 대상으로 선택하지 않을 것 같습니다 .
He is highly recommended by the Editors of Financial Introduce.
그는 Financial Introduce 편집자들의 적극 추천을 받았습니다.
He said Ms. Xu is experienced in various aspects
그는 Xu 씨가 다양한 측면에서 경험이 있다고 말했습니다.
and the quality of the writing is quite consistent.
그리고 글쓰기의 질은 상당히 일관적입니다.
If this is just a question and answer, there's no need to meet me directly.
이것이 단지 질문과 답변이라면 굳이 저를 직접 만날 필요는 없습니다.
Submitting an answer is enough.
답변을 제출하는 것으로 충분합니다.
Interviews should be like chatting and self-reflection.
인터뷰는 수다 와 자기 반성 과 같아야 합니다 .
I like Ms. Zheng.
저는 Zheng 씨를 좋아해요.
Sorry for my bad judgment.
잘못된 판단을 해서 죄송합니다.
I'll reschedule.
일정을 다시 잡겠습니다.
ZHU XING GUO'S OPINION ON THE CURRENCY WAR
통화 전쟁에 대한 ZHU XING GUO의 견해
Mrs. Yi, do you want to meet me?
이씨, 저를 만나시겠어요?
Well, see you later.
그럼 나중에 보자.
You don't need to comfort me.
나를 위로할 필요는 없어요.
I understand. I'm fine.
이해합니다. 잘 지내요.
Understand what?
뭘 이해해?
I know you want to talk about the interview with Shi Yan.
당신이 Shi Yan과의 인터뷰에 관해 이야기하고 싶어한다는 것을 압니다 .
I understand.
이해합니다.
Yu Ling is more experienced than me.
Yu Ling은 나보다 경험이 많습니다.
Although a little disappointed,
조금 실망하긴 했지만,
My interview draft can still be improved.
내 인터뷰 초안은 아직 개선될 수 있습니다.
So, no need to regret.
그러므로 후회할 필요가 없습니다.
I'll prepare better next time.
다음에는 더 잘 준비하겠습니다 .
You're dressed very nicely today.
오늘 아주 멋지게 옷을 입었군요.
Today is my girlfriend's birthday.
오늘은 내 여자친구의 생일이다.
I want to look beautiful in his eyes.
나는 그의 눈에 아름답게 보이고 싶다.
Looking from another point of view, if I interviewed Shi Yan,
다른 관점에서 보면, 시옌을 인터뷰했다면,
I won't be able to celebrate with my girlfriend tonight.
오늘 밤에는 여자친구와 함께 축하할 수 없을 것 같아요 .
So, this is indeed good.
그러니 이것은 정말 좋은 것입니다.
Okay.
좋아요.
What's wrong, Mrs. Yi?
무슨 일이에요, 이씨?
Yunchuang staff just called me.
방금 Yunchuang 직원이 전화했어요.
They said for tonight's interview,
오늘 밤 인터뷰에서 그들은 이렇게 말했습니다.
Shi Yan has already appointed you
Shi Yan이 이미 당신을 임명했습니다
to do it.
그것을하기 위해.
Too bad, you're celebrating your girlfriend's birthday tonight.
안타깝지만 오늘 밤 당신은 여자친구의 생일을 축하하게 됩니다.
I guess you don't have time, right?
시간이 없을 것 같은데요, 그렇죠?
Shi Yan pointed at me?
Shi Yan이 나를 가리킨다고요?
Yes, he chose you in the end.
그래, 그는 결국 당신을 선택했습니다.
Tonight.
오늘 밤.
Do you mind?
괜찮으세요?
No, I can.
아니요, 할 수 있습니다.
Are you sure?
확실합니까?
Great, tonight at 19.00.
좋습니다. 오늘 밤 19시입니다.
Shi Yan's assistant will talk to you about the details.
Shi Yan의 조수가 자세한 내용을 알려드릴 것입니다 .
OK, I'll get ready right away.
알았어, 바로 준비할게.
Wait.
기다리다.
What about your boyfriend?
당신의 남자 친구는 어떻습니까?
Birthdays come every year,
매년 찾아오는 생일,
but the opportunity to interview Shi Yan was rare.
그러나 Shi Yan을 인터뷰할 기회는 드물었습니다.
If I finish everything as quickly as possible,
최대한 빨리 모든 일을 끝내면 ,
maybe there's still time to celebrate before midnight.
어쩌면 자정 이전에 축하할 시간이 아직 남아 있을 수도 있습니다 .
You are like that, Zheng Shu Yi.
당신도 그렇군요, 정수이.
Mr. Shi, exclusive interview details have been arranged.
Shi 씨, 독점 인터뷰 세부 사항이 준비되었습니다.
How about we schedule the interview in the main conference room?
인터뷰 일정을 본 회의실에서 잡는 게 어때요 ?
Wasn't Le'an's representative scheduled to come ?
Le'an 대표가 올 예정이 아니었나요?
for a meeting in the afternoon?
오후에 회의 때문에?
Department One has already booked the main conference room for the afternoon,
1부서는 이미 오후에 메인 회의실을 예약해두었고 ,
but they canceled it.
하지만 그들은 그것을 취소했습니다.
It seems they have rescheduled the meeting
회의 일정을 다시 잡은 것 같아요
with representatives from Lieying and Le'an in the morning.
아침에는 Lieying과 Le'an의 대표자들과 함께 .
Both in the morning?
둘 다 아침에?
Yes, the system shows it is rescheduled
예, 시스템에 일정이 변경된 것으로 표시됩니다
personally by Mr. Feng from Department One.
개인적으로 1부서의 Mr. Feng이 직접 작성했습니다 .
Fan, drop me off somewhere.
팬님, 저를 어딘가에 내려주세요.
I have to go back to the company.
회사로 돌아가야 해요.
OK, Mr. Shi.
알았어, 시 씨.
What about Ms. Qin?
진 씨는 어떻습니까?
Invite him and take him back to the Shi family's wastu.
그를 초대하고 그를 Shi 가족의 wastu로 다시 데려가십시오.
Ya, Pak.
응, 박.
Amazing!
놀라운!
You've got the headlines for nine issues this year.
올해 9개 이슈의 헤드라인을 확인하셨습니다 .
This has never happened in our magazine.
우리 잡지에서는 이런 일이 일어난 적이 없습니다 .
Even Bu Yi's record is only eight editions in a year.
부이의 기록조차 1년에 8판밖에 되지 않는다.
Do you still drink coffee? Do you want to be better?
아직도 커피를 드시나요? 더 나아지고 싶나요?
Drink this instead.
대신 이것을 마셔보세요.
Why do you think Yunchuang
윤추앙은 왜 그렇게 생각하는가?
suddenly change journalists for interviews?
갑자기 인터뷰를 위해 기자를 바꾸나요?
This shows that their boss has sharp eyes.
이는 상사의 눈이 예리하다는 것을 보여준다.
We mean, Shi Yan?
시얀 말인가요?
Shi Yan obviously had sharp eyes.
Shi Yan은 분명히 날카로운 눈을 가지고 있었습니다.
Otherwise, he would not be able to change Mingyu Yunchuang
그렇지 않으면 민규 윤추앙을 바꿀 수 없을 것이다.
became a huge success in just a few years.
불과 몇 년 만에 큰 성공을 거두었습니다 .
But he's also a bit strange.
그런데 그 사람도 좀 이상해요.
When Mingyu Group faced its most difficult time,
민규그룹이 가장 어려운 시기를 맞이했을 때,
he left his family's company
그는 가족이 다니던 회사를 떠났다
and start a new company.
그리고 새로운 회사를 시작하세요.
What was he thinking?
그는 무슨 생각을 하고 있었나요?
You don't know how cruel the rumors about him are,
그에 대한 소문이 얼마나 잔혹한지 너는 모르지 .
people call him the runaway prince,
사람들은 그를 도망친 왕자라고 부른다 .
selfish cowards, and others.
이기적인 겁쟁이 등.
Also, his girlfriend, actress Bei Lin.
그리고 그의 여자친구인 배우 베이린.
They said he immediately threw it away.
바로 버렸다고 하더군요 .
Actually, I think he's quite brave.
사실 내 생각엔 그 사람 꽤 용감한 것 같아.
Despite all their doubts,
그들의 모든 의심에도 불구하고,
he still chose that path.
그는 여전히 그 길을 선택했습니다.
That takes great courage.
그러기 위해서는 큰 용기가 필요합니다.
What an honor for us
우리에게 얼마나 영광입니까?
if you can establish a partnership with Lieying.
Lieying과 파트너십을 맺을 수 있다면 .
Mr. Feng, you are too kind.
펑 씨, 당신은 너무 친절해요.
-We are family. -Yes.
-우리는 가족. -예.
Appropriate. We've been friends for years.
적절한. 우리는 수년간 친구였습니다 .
Of.
의.
Pak Shi.
박시.
Get two cold colas from the kitchen.
주방에서 차가운 콜라 두 잔을 가져오세요.
Ya, Pak.
응, 박.
I've been working on an article about Lieying lately.
나는 최근 Lieying에 관한 기사를 작성하고 있습니다 .
They said that Yunchuang is considering investment.
윤추앙은 투자를 고려하고 있다고 한다.
You know about Lieying, right?
리잉에 대해 아시죠?
They have gained attention in recent years.
그들은 최근 몇 년 동안 주목을 받았습니다 .
Many companies are willing to invest in them.
많은 기업들이 이에 투자할 의향이 있습니다.
There wasn't a single clear picture of Shi Yan on the internet.
인터넷에는 Shi Yan의 선명한 사진이 단 한 장도 없었습니다 .
He became more humble
그는 더욱 겸손해졌다
and never appeared in front of the press after starting his company.
회사를 시작한 이후에는 언론 앞에 한 번도 모습을 드러내지 않았습니다 .
If we can record exclusive video or audio of him
그 사람의 독점 영상이나 음성을 녹음할 수 있다면
for our digital magazine,
디지털 매거진의 경우
it will definitely attract many readers.
확실히 많은 독자들을 끌어들일 것입니다.
Are you still thinking about upgrading your digital magazine?
아직도 디지털 매거진을 업그레이드할 생각을 하고 계십니까 ?
Financial information is closely related to everyone.
금융정보는 모든 사람과 밀접한 관련이 있습니다.
If we don't fix it
우리가 고치지 않으면
and stick to the same content as the print version,
인쇄본과 동일한 내용을 고수하고 ,
without effective interaction with readers,
독자와의 효과적인 상호작용 없이 ,
we will only fall further behind.
우리는 더욱 뒤쳐질 뿐입니다.
You're right too.
당신 말이 맞아요.
But our magazine currently has no human resources or funds
하지만 우리 잡지에는 현재 인력이나 자금이 없습니다.
for updates to this digital magazine.
이 디지털 매거진의 업데이트를 확인하세요.
Even if you convince Mrs. Yi,
이씨 부인을 설득하더라도
he will definitely ask you,
그 사람은 분명히 너한테 물어볼 거야.
who will do it, how,
누가, 어떻게 할 것인가 ?
and where the funds come from.
자금이 어디서 나오는지.
I will do it.
나는 그것을 할 것이다.
I want the higher ups to see
윗분들이 보셨으면 좋겠어요
if I have the ability to lead the updating of digital magazines.
디지털 매거진의 업데이트를 주도할 수 있는 능력이 있다면 .
Then, by monetizing the content,
그러면 콘텐츠로 수익을 창출하여,
we can get human resources and funds
인적자원과 자금을 확보할 수 있다
from the updated digital magazine.
업데이트된 디지털 매거진에서.
What a bold idea!
정말 대담한 아이디어입니다!
Go for it. I support you!
그것을 위해 가십시오. 나는 너를지지 해!
You should stop by our place more often .
우리 집에 더 자주 들러야 합니다.
Of course.
물론.
-Hai, Pak Shi.
-하이, 박시 - 하이, 박시
This is a cold drink.
이것은 차가운 음료입니다.
Thank you, Mr. Shi.
고마워요, 시 씨.
By the way,
그런데,
I saw your latest data and information on my way here.
여기 오는 길에 당신의 최신 데이터와 정보를 봤어요 .
-The progress is very impressive. -Yes.
-진행이 매우 인상적입니다. -예.
We just finished it last night.
우리는 어젯밤에 그걸 끝냈어요.
Lily, please take Mr. Chen to the meeting room next door.
릴리 씨, 첸 선생님을 옆집 회의실로 데려가 주세요 .
I'll follow soon.
곧 따라가겠습니다.
OK, Mr. Shi. Mr. Chen, please follow me.
알았어, 시 씨. 첸 씨, 저를 따라오세요.
Pak Shi.
박시.
Mr. Shi Yan, if you have any requests, feel free to say so.
Shi Yan씨, 요청사항이 있으시면 언제든지 말씀해 주세요.
After all, we have a close relationship with Mingyu.
결국 우리는 민규와 긴밀한 관계를 맺고 있다.
Over the last two years,
지난 2년 동안,
we also do business with your father.
우리는 또한 당신의 아버지와 사업을합니다.
Of course, considering the circumstances at that time,
물론 당시 상황을 고려하면
We definitely want to help.
우리는 확실히 돕고 싶습니다.
So, I'm sure
그래서 나는 확신한다
we will work well together this time.
이번에는 잘 협력 하겠습니다 .
Mr. Shi, do you have any questions?
시 씨, 질문 있으신가요?
Thank You.
감사합니다.
I've reviewed the situation with Lieying,
리잉님과 상황을 검토해 보았는데 ,
but that's what interests me more
하지만 그게 더 관심이 있는 거야
is the direction of your company in the future.
회사의 미래 방향입니다.
Our company is among the top leaders in this industry.
우리 회사는 이 업계 최고의 리더 중 하나입니다.
As for Le'an Technology,
Le'an Technology의 경우,
they used to be one of our suppliers.
그들은 우리의 공급업체 중 하나였습니다 .
This has nothing to do with position in the industry.
이는 업계에서의 지위와는 아무런 관련이 없습니다 .
According to information,
정보에 따르면,
If your company's main goal is to serve the wider community,
회사의 주요 목표가 더 넓은 지역 사회에 봉사하는 것이라면,
there must be further technological progress .
더 많은 기술적 진보가 있어야 합니다.
But so far I haven't seen a solution.
그러나 지금까지 나는 해결책을 보지 못했습니다.
Mr. Shi, this is the problem.
시 씨, 이것이 문제입니다.
Lieying is a well-established company.
Lieying은 잘 확립된 회사입니다.
Investing in them will help us enter this industry quickly.
이들에 대한 투자는 우리가 이 산업에 빠르게 진입하는 데 도움이 될 것입니다.
Apart from that, Lieying has a close relationship with Mingyu.
그 외에도 리잉은 민규와 친분이 두터운 편이다.
We have gone through ups and downs together.
우리는 우여곡절을 함께 겪었습니다 .
Correct.
옳은.
Yes, I understand.
네 이해했습니다.
My father respects Lieying very much.
아버지는 리잉을 매우 존경하십니다.
But business is still business.
하지만 사업은 여전히 ​​사업이다.
The essence of investing is buying future value.
투자의 본질은 미래가치를 사는 것이다.
If Lieying is willing to cooperate with Yunchuang,
Lieying이 Yunchuang과 협력할 의향이 있다면
You have to make a plan to upgrade your core technology.
핵심기술을 업그레이드할 계획을 세워야 합니다 .
After all, we are an investment company,
결국 우리는 투자회사이기 때문에
not a charity.
자선 단체가 아닙니다.
Don't you agree?
동의하지 않나요?
Thank you for your valuable time today.
오늘 귀중한 시간을 내주셔서 감사합니다 .
Mr. Feng, please take Mr. Li away.
펑 씨, 리 씨를 데려가 주세요.
Pak Li.
박 리.
- Mr. Li. - Mr. Chen, please pass by here.
- 리 씨. - 첸 선생님, 여기 좀 지나가주세요.
Technical breakthroughs take time,
기술적 혁신에는 시간이 걸립니다.
but once achieved,
하지만 일단 달성하면
it would be a revolutionary boost to our domestic chip production.
이는 우리 국내 칩 생산에 혁명적인 발전이 될 것입니다 .
So, keep up the good work
그러니 계속해서 좋은 일을 하세요
and create our own patent.
그리고 우리만의 특허를 만들어 보세요.
I have high hopes for you.
나는 당신에게 큰 기대를 갖고 있습니다.
Yunchuang will provide you with maximum support.
Yunchuang은 귀하에게 최대한의 지원을 제공할 것입니다 .
Thank you, Mr. Shi.
고마워요, 시 씨.
If we can solve the research and development funding problem,
연구개발 자금 문제를 해결할 수 있다면 ,
I am very confident that we can achieve significant progress.
저는 우리가 상당한 진전을 이룰 수 있다고 확신합니다 .
I will visit Le'an again tomorrow.
내일 다시 Le'an을 방문하겠습니다.
-We can discuss further. -Okay, I have to go.
- 좀 더 논의해 보겠습니다. - 알았어, 가야 해.
Pak Shi,
박시,
I'll be straight forward.
나는 곧장 말할 것이다.
The owner of Lieying, Mr. Li, is an old friend of your father and Mr. Tian.
Lieying의 주인인 Mr. Li는 당신의 아버지와 Mr. Tian의 오랜 친구입니다.
If you insist on choosing Le'an,
굳이 Le'an을 선택한다면,
I'm afraid it won't be easy to convince the council.
의회를 설득하기가 쉽지 않을 것 같습니다.
Meetings are a fundamental part of investing.
회의는 투자의 기본입니다 .
If you can't even schedule a meeting with a potential partner,
잠재적인 파트너와의 미팅 일정 조차 잡을 수 없다면 ,
how can I trust your assessment of this project?
이 프로젝트에 대한 당신의 평가를 어떻게 믿을 수 있나요 ?
Mingyu's investment is based on future trends,
민규의 투자는 미래 트렌드를 바탕으로,
not a personal connection.
개인적인 인연이 아닙니다.
Pak Tian.
박태안.
Mr. Shi suddenly came during our meeting today.
오늘 회의 중에 시 선생님이 갑자기 오셨습니다 .
Hai, Pak Shi.
하이, 박시.
(Uncle, didn't you promise to pick me up today?)
(삼촌, 오늘 나를 데리러 오기로 약속하지 않았나요 ?)
There's something urgent.
급한 일이 있어요.
(Uncle, don't you love me anymore?)
(삼촌, 이제 저를 사랑하지 않나요?)
Pak Shi.
박시.
I have to go. We will talk again later.
나는 가야 해요. 나중에 다시 이야기하겠습니다.
I've put Ms. Qin.
진 씨를 넣었어요.
He complained because you didn't pick him up yourself
당신이 직접 데리러 오지 않아서 그 사람이 불평했어요
and asked me to convey his complaint.
그리고 자신의 불만을 전달해달라고 요청했습니다.
Is there anything else?
다른 것이 있나요?
Yes, Mr. Guan Ji said he couldn't contact you by phone.
네, 관지씨가 전화로는 연락이 안 된다고 하더군요.
What he wants?
그가 원하는 것은 무엇입니까?
Pak Guan Ji held a dinner today at Warner Estate.
박관지는 오늘 워너 에스테이트에서 만찬을 가졌다.
He insisted you attend.
그는 당신이 참석하라고 주장했습니다.
I am busy.
저는 바쁩니다.
Mr. Guan Ji had anticipated you would say that.
관지 씨는 당신이 그렇게 말할 것이라고 예상했습니다.
He said there was an important person he wanted to introduce to you.
소개하고 싶은 중요한 사람이 있다고 하더군요 .
YU YOU
유 당신
OK, tell him I'll come tonight.
알았어, 내가 오늘 밤에 올 거라고 전해줘 .
How about tonight's Financial Introduction interview?
오늘 밤 금융 소개 인터뷰 어때요 ?
Explain the situation to them and reschedule.
상황을 설명하고 일정을 변경하세요.
Fine, I'll do it right away.
좋아요, 바로 할게요.
(Honey, you're not working overtime today, are you?)
(여보, 오늘은 야근 안 하시나요?)
Xing Zhou,
저우싱,
do you remember the interview with Shi Yan that I told you about?
내가 말했던 Shi Yan과의 인터뷰를 기억하시나요 ?
Bu Yi just told me
부이가 방금 나한테 말했어
if they have changed journalists
기자가 바뀌었다면
to interview Shi Yan. I'm doing it now.
Shi Yan을 인터뷰하기 위해. 지금 하고 있어요.
(But my birthday is only once a year.)
(근데 내 생일은 1년에 한 번뿐이다.)
I'm sorry, Xing Zhou.
미안해요, 저우싱.
I've been preparing for this interview for over two months.
저는 이 인터뷰를 두 달 넘게 준비했습니다 .
This is truly a rare opportunity.
정말 흔치 않은 기회입니다.
He asked me specifically.
그는 나에게 구체적으로 물었다.
If I don't come, we won't have a headline for the next issue.
내가 오지 않으면 다음 호의 헤드라인이 나오지 않을 것입니다.
You know how many stories he has.
당신은 그가 얼마나 많은 이야기를 가지고 있는지 알고 있습니다.
He hasn't done any interviews since founding Mingyu Yunchuang.
그는 Mingyu Yunchuang을 창립한 이후 인터뷰를 한 적이 없습니다 .
This will be his first exclusive interview.
이번이 그의 첫 단독 인터뷰 가 될 것이다 .
(Alright. I guess we can celebrate later.)
(알겠습니다. 나중에 축하해도 될 것 같아요.)
(I'll wait for you downstairs after my work is finished.)
( 내 일이 끝난 후에 아래층에서 기다릴게요 .)
I'm sorry, Xing Zhou.
미안해요, 저우싱.
This is very sudden.
이것은 매우 갑작스러운 일입니다.
(I understand.)
(이해합니다.)
(You've done a lot of preparation for this interview.)
(이 인터뷰를 위해 많은 준비를 하셨습니다 .)
(You should make the most of it .)
(당신은 그것을 최대한 활용해야합니다
Thank you, Xing Zhou.
고마워요, Xing Zhou.
You are the best.
너는 최고야.
Interviews start at 19.00.
면접은 19시부터 시작됩니다.
I'll try to finish it within two hours.
두 시간 안에 끝내도록 노력하겠습니다 .
There's still time to see you, blow out the candles, make a wish,
아직 당신을 만날 시간이 있고, 촛불을 끄고, 소원을 빌고,
and enjoy birthday cake.
그리고 생일 케이크를 즐기세요.
(I'll come pick you up later.)
(나중에 데리러 올게요.)
I'll send you my location later.
나중에 내 위치를 보내드리겠습니다.
You are so kind.
당신은 정말 친절해요.
So, your boyfriend doesn't mind?
그럼 네 남자친구는 상관없지?
Yes, he understood and even offered to pick me up.
예, 그는 이해했고 심지어 나를 데리러 오겠다고 제안했습니다.
Your boyfriend seems too understanding.
네 남자친구는 너무 이해심이 많은 것 같아.
Unlike my boyfriend, he is very possessive.
내 남자친구와는 다르게 그는 소유욕이 강해요.
If I cancel my promise just once,
한 번만 약속을 취소하면
whatever the reason, he will be angry with me.
이유가 무엇이든 그는 나에게 화를 낼 것입니다.
Let's go.
갑시다.
(Halo, Nn. Zheng. Aku Chen Sheng dari Mingyu Yunchuang.)
(Halo, Nn. Zheng. Aku Chen Sheng dari Mingyu Yunchuang.)
Hello Pak Chen.
안녕하세요 박첸님.
Ms. Zheng, Mr. Shi has to cancel
Zheng 씨, Shi 씨는 취소해야 합니다
interview tonight for personal reasons.
개인적인 이유로 오늘 밤에 인터뷰를 합니다 .
We need to reschedule.
일정을 다시 조정해야 해요.
(We are very sorry.)
(우리는 매우 유감 스럽습니다.)
What day does Mr. Shi want to reschedule the interview?
Shi 선생님은 인터뷰 일정을 언제로 변경하고 싶으신가요 ?
(How about the same day next week?)
( 다음 주 같은 날은 어때요 ?)
(Or is there a convenient time for you next week?)
(아니면 다음 주에 편한 시간이 있으신가요?)
If we reschedule for next week,
다음주로 일정을 변경한다면 ,
We don't have a headline for the next issue.
다음 호에는 헤드라인이 없습니다 .
Can Mr. Shi spare some time in the next two days?
Shi 씨가 앞으로 이틀 동안 시간을 ​​좀 낼 수 있을까요 ?
The timing is not a problem.
타이밍은 문제가되지 않습니다.
We can even divide it into two sessions.
두 세션으로 나눌 수도 있습니다 .
I think that's impossible.
나는 그것이 불가능하다고 생각한다.
(Mr Shi's schedule for the next two days is already full.)
(시 씨의 다음 이틀 일정은 이미 꽉 찼습니다.)
So...
그래서...
How about spending two hours tonight?
오늘 밤 두 시간을 보내는 게 어때요 ?
One hour is not a problem.
1시간은 문제가 되지 않습니다.
Mr. Shi has personal matters tonight.
오늘 밤 Shi 씨는 개인적인 문제가 있습니다.
He couldn't spare the time.
그는 시간을 아끼지 못했습니다.
(We're really sorry.)
(정말 죄송합니다.)
Wait...
기다리다...
Shan Shan, you are beautiful and have many connections.
Shan Shan, 당신은 아름답고 인맥이 많습니다.
Can you help me find out where Shi Yan will be tonight?
오늘 밤 Shi Yan이 어디에 있는지 알아낼 수 있나요 ?
Halo.
후광.
Shi Yan?
시얀?
I don't know him.
나는 그를 모른다.
But you're lucky.
하지만 당신은 운이 좋다.
(I know Shi Yan's good friend, Guan Ji,)
(저는 Shi Yan의 좋은 친구인 Guan Ji를 알고 있습니다.)
(holding a private banquet at Warner Estate tonight.)
( 오늘 밤 Warner Estate에서 비공개 연회를 개최합니다 .)
(I think there are many people in Jiangcheng)
(강성에는 사람이 많은 것 같아요)
(Those with connections to Guan Capital will attend.)
(관 캐피탈과 인연이 있는 분들이 참석합니다.)
(I'm not sure if Shi Yan will be there.)
( 시얀이 거기에 있을지는 잘 모르겠습니다 .)
Well then, I'll try my luck.
그럼, 행운을 시험해 보겠습니다.
(Wait.)
(기다리다.)
(Aren't you supposed to celebrate)
(축하해야 하는 거 아냐?)
(Yue Xing Zhou's birthday tonight?)
(오늘 밤 Yue Xing Zhou의 생일인가요?)
(You're going to cancel?)
(취소하실 건가요?)
I can't miss Shi Yan, right?
Shi Yan을 놓칠 수 없겠죠?
(Okay.)
(좋아요.)
(Career-focused women are the most charming.)
(경력 중심의 여성이 가장 매력적입니다.)
Thank you for your kind words.
좋은 말 해줘서 고마워.
Warner Estate.
워너 에스테이트.
Enjoy.
즐기다.
Come here.
이리 오세요.
Mr. Chen, good evening.
첸 씨, 안녕하세요.
I'm at Warner Estate now.
저는 지금 워너 에스테이트에 있어요.
(Ms. Zheng, how did you...)
(정씨, 어떻게 지내셨나요...)
I'm sorry for coming uninvited,
초대받지도 않은 채 와서 미안해요 .
but this is an urgent matter.
하지만 이건 긴급한 문제야.
Can you tell Mr. Shi that I can wait for him here?
Shi 씨에게 제가 여기서 그를 기다릴 수 있다고 말씀해 주시겠습니까 ?
Hopefully he can feel my sincerity
그 사람도 내 진심을 느낄 수 있었으면 좋겠어
and make time for interviews.
그리고 인터뷰 시간을 내세요.
That's it, find a place and wait.
그게 다야, 장소를 찾아 기다리십시오.
I'll talk to Mr. Shi,
내가 Shi 선생님과 얘기 좀 할게요.
but I can't guarantee that he will have time to meet you.
하지만 그 사람이 당신을 만날 시간이 있을지는 장담할 수 없어요 .
(Most likely you came here in vain.)
(대부분 당신은 여기에 헛되이 왔을 것입니다.)
I understand. Whatever happens, I am very grateful to you.
이해합니다. 무슨 일이 있어도 나는 당신에게 매우 감사합니다.
I think Guan Ji held this banquet
내 생각엔 Guan Ji가 이 연회를 주최한 것 같아
for everyone to eat and drink.
모두가 먹고 마실 수 있도록.
It can't be that simple.
그렇게 간단할 수는 없습니다.
Kudengar Yu You
쿠덴가 유 유
specially recruited by Guan Capital from abroad.
관캐피털이 해외에서 특별히 채용한 것입니다.
He is a professor at the University of Finance and Economics.
그는 금융경제대학교의 교수이다 .
Only Guan Capital has the power
관자본만이 힘을 가지고 있다
to hire him as a consultant.
그를 컨설턴트로 고용하기 위해.
I see his son Shi is also here.
그의 아들 Shi도 여기에 있는 것을 봅니다.
Shi Wen Guang's son was very unreliable.
Shi Wen Guang의 아들은 매우 신뢰할 수 없었습니다.
When Mingyu was in trouble, he started his own company.
민규는 어려움에 처하자 회사를 차렸다.
Shi Wen Guang was forced to entrust the company
Shi Wen Guang은 회사를 위임해야 했습니다.
to his son-in-law and those outsiders.
그의 사위와 그 외부인들에게.
Exaggeration.
과장.
From what I see, two young men from the Guan and Shi families
내가 보기엔 관씨 가문과 시 가문의 두 젊은이가
quite ambitious.
꽤 야심적이에요.
By bringing professors from abroad,
해외에서 교수님들을 모셔와서 ,
they might be planning to make a breakthrough.
그들은 돌파구를 만들 계획을 세울 수도 있습니다 .
One is shy and the other likes to have fun.
한 사람은 수줍음이 많고 다른 사람은 즐거운 시간을 보내는 것을 좋아합니다.
What breakthroughs can they make?
그들은 어떤 획기적인 발전을 이룰 수 있습니까?
It is impossible. Come on.
불가능하다. 어서 해봐요.
Is Guan Ji late again?
관지 또 늦었어?
Mr. Guan Ji said he was stuck in traffic,
Guan Ji 씨는 교통 체증에 갇혔다고 하더군요.
but it will be here in ten minutes.
하지만 10분 안에 도착할 거예요 .
Is there anything else?
다른 것이 있나요?
Ms. Zheng from Financial Introduction is also here.
Financial Introduction의 Ms. Zheng 도 여기에 있습니다.
He said he would wait for you
그 사람이 당신을 기다리겠다고 하더군요
and hope you can find time to do an interview tonight.
그리고 오늘 밤에 인터뷰할 시간을 찾을 수 있기를 바랍니다.
Zheng Shu Yi?
정수이?
Didn't I ask to reschedule?
내가 일정을 변경하라고 요청하지 않았나요 ?
I've told him,
나는 그에게 말했습니다.
but he said that the interview was cancelled,
그런데 인터뷰가 취소됐다고 하더군요 .
The next issue of the magazine had no headline.
그 잡지의 다음 호에는 헤드라인이 없었습니다.
I don't know how he knows about your personal schedule.
그 사람이 당신의 개인 일정을 어떻게 아는지는 모르겠어요 .
I have a meeting at Le'an Technology tomorrow,
내일 Le'an Technology에서 회의가 있는데 ,
so I don't have time for an interview tonight.
그래서 오늘 밤에는 인터뷰할 시간이 없어요 .
Since he came all the way here, probably hasn't eaten yet.
여기까지 왔으니까 아마 아직 식사도 안 했을 거예요.
Prepare food and a car to take him home.
그를 집으로 데려갈 음식과 차를 준비하세요 .
It's hard to get a taxi here.
여기서는 택시 잡기가 어렵습니다.
Ya, Pak Shi.
응, 박시.
Graduated from Harvard University with a full scholarship.
하버드 대학교를 전액 장학금으로 졸업했습니다.
Double PhD degree in Economics and Finance from Cambridge University!
케임브리지 대학교에서 경제 및 금융학 박사 학위를 두 번 취득하세요 !
Soon became the youngest professor at the University of Finance and Economics.
곧 재경대학 최연소 교수가 됐다 .
Impressive resume.
인상적인 이력서.
-Thank You. -You're welcome.
-감사합니다. -천만에요.
Wait.
기다리다.
Are you Yu You? Professor Yu?
당신은 Yu You입니까? 유 교수님?
You know me?
저를 아시나요?
I've read some of your papers.
나는 당신의 논문 중 일부를 읽었습니다.
Financial technology, technology-based financial innovation,
금융기술, 기술기반 금융혁신,
not only has an impact on macroeconomics,
거시경제에 영향을 미칠 뿐만 아니라,
also has the potential to bring major changes to our daily lives.
또한 우리 일상생활에 큰 변화를 가져올 가능성도 있습니다 .
I feel a close connection to this field
나는 이 분야와 밀접한 관계를 느낀다
because it is very relevant to everyday life.
일상생활과 매우 밀접하기 때문입니다 .
Correct. That is also the reason I chose this research direction.
옳은. 이것이 제가 이 연구 방향을 선택한 이유이기도 합니다 .
In the past, finance and capital seemed like a luxurious concept,
과거에는 금융과 자본이 사치스러운 개념처럼 보였지만,
but now we are exploring
하지만 지금 우리는 탐험 중이에요
how it can change our life to what extent.
그것이 우리의 삶을 어느 정도까지 변화시킬 수 있는지.
If you have the chance,
기회가 된다면,
I want to return to my alma mater
모교로 돌아가고 싶어요
and attended some of your lectures, Professor Yu.
유 교수님 의 강의에도 참석하셨습니다 .
Are you a graduate of the University of Finance and Economics?
재정경제대학교 졸업생이신가요 ?
Yes, currently I work at Financial Introduction.
네, 현재 저는 Financial Introduction에서 근무하고 있습니다.
I'm a journalist.
저는 저널리스트입니다.
Professor Yu, can we be friends on WeChat?
유 교수님, 우리 위챗에서 친구가 될 수 있나요?
- Mr. Shi. -Of course.
- 시 씨. -물론.
-I'll scan your code. -Good.
-코드를 스캔하겠습니다. -좋은.
Itu Zheng Shu Yi dari Financial Introduce.
Itu Zheng Shu Yi dari 금융을 소개합니다.
Finished.
완성된.
Zheng Shu Yi. I'll put "journalist".
정슈이. "저널리스트"라고 입력하겠습니다.
Thank You.
감사합니다.
Zheng Shu Yi?
정수이?
Winner of Best Journalist this year
올해 최우수 언론인상 수상
is an article journalist
기사 기자야
"Zhu Xing Guo's Opinion on the Currency War,"
" 환율전쟁에 대한 주싱궈의 견해 "
Zheng Shu Yi.
정슈이.
Excuse me. I'm late.
실례합니다. 나는 늦었다.
Guan Ji, it's been a long time since you rode a horse with me.
관지 씨, 나와 함께 말을 타본 지 오랜만이에요 .
My fault.
내 잘못.
I heard you went to Qionghai, so I waited for you to come back.
Qionghai에 갔다고해서 돌아 오기를 기다렸습니다.
I'm back now.
나는 지금 돌아왔다.
Then, I will wait for you at the equestrian club tomorrow.
그럼 내일 승마클럽에서 기다리겠습니다 .
As far as I know,
내가 아는 한,
Tonight's banquet is not open to the media.
오늘 밤 연회는 언론에 공개되지 않습니다.
Yes, I came personally to wait for the interviewee.
네, 제가 직접 인터뷰 대상자를 기다리러 왔습니다.
Work is important, and so is your health.
일도 중요 하고 건강도 중요합니다.
You don't look well.
당신은 표정이 좋지 않습니다.
No, I'll be fine after taking the medicine.
아니요, 약을 먹으면 괜찮아질 거예요 .
We went in first.
우리가 먼저 들어갔다.
Of.
의.
I have to go.
나는 가야 해요.
Come in.
올.
Pak Shi!
박시!
Sorry, Ms. Zheng. Mr. Shi really doesn't have time tonight,
미안해요, 정 씨. Shi 씨는 오늘 밤 정말 시간이 없어요.
but I will arrange an interview as soon as possible.
하지만 가능한 한 빨리 인터뷰를 준비 하겠습니다 .
You haven't had dinner yet, have you?
아직 저녁을 안 드셨나요?
Please eat first
먼저 드세요
and I will prepare a car to take you home.
그리고 당신을 집으로 데려갈 차를 준비하겠습니다 .
It doesn't matter. Someone picked me up.
그것은 중요하지 않습니다. 누군가 나를 데리러 왔습니다.
I almost succeeded.
나는 거의 성공했다.
At least, let me see what you look like.
적어도 당신이 어떻게 생겼는지 보여주세요.
-Long time no see. -Yes, that's right, Mr. Zhang.
-오랜만이에요. -네, 맞습니다, 장 씨.
-Pleased to meet you.
-만나서 반갑습니다.
Mr. Wang, how are you?
왕 씨, 잘 지내세요?
Hello, Professor Yu.
안녕하세요 유교수님.
Welcome back to China.
중국에 다시 오신 것을 환영합니다.
Hello, Mr. Shi. Thank You.
안녕하세요, 시 씨. 감사합니다.
I read your research
나는 당신의 연구를 읽었습니다
regarding the impact of financial limitations
재정적 한계의 영향에 관해
on the financing behavior of public companies.
공기업의 자금조달 행태 에 대해 .
This differs from many domestic perspectives.
이는 많은 국내 관점과 다릅니다.
That's ancient thinking.
그것은 고대의 생각입니다.
This is getting quite long.
꽤 길어지고 있습니다.
My thinking has evolved this year.
올해 내 생각이 발전했습니다.
Accepting change is the right way.
변화를 받아들이는 것이 올바른 방법입니다.
I'm glad Guan Ji recruited you.
Guan Ji가 당신을 채용하게 되어 기쁘게 생각합니다.
There are definitely plenty of opportunities
분명 기회는 많을 거야
for us to ask for your advice.
우리가 당신의 조언을 구하도록 해주세요.
Mr. Shi, you flatter me.
Shi 씨, 당신은 나에게 아첨합니다.
Yunchuang's future is limitless.
Yunchuang의 미래는 무한합니다.
We can learn from each other.
우리는 서로에게서 배울 수 있습니다.
By the way,
그런데,
Some time ago, I read an article
얼마전에 기사를 읽었는데
"Zhu Xing Guo's Opinion on the Currency War."
“ 환율전쟁에 대한 주싱궈(Zhu Xing Guo)의 견해.”
The viewing angles are sharp.
시야각이 날카롭습니다.
His writing is insightful and deep. That's quite inspiring.
그의 글은 통찰력이 있고 깊다. 정말 감동적이네요.
You might want to take a look if you have time.
시간이 있으면 한 번 살펴보시면 좋을 것 같습니다 .
I remember the article vaguely.
기사가 어렴풋이 기억나네요.
It's well written.
잘 쓰여졌네요.
Cheers.
건배.
Ladies and gentlemen, may I ask for your attention?
신사 숙녀 여러분, 주목해 주시겠습니까?
Today we gather here,
오늘 우리는 여기에 모였습니다.
and all of you are old friends of Guan Capital.
그리고 여러분 모두는 Guan Capital의 오랜 친구입니다.
Towards the end of the year, I held this banquet
연말에 이 연회를 열었어요
as a token of thanks for our sincere cooperation.
우리의 진심 어린 협력에 대한 감사의 표시로 .
We want to officially introduce new friends at once.
우리는 새로운 친구들을 정식으로 한 번에 소개하고 싶습니다.
Our strategic advisor,
우리의 전략 고문,
Mr Yu You, a finance professor.
금융 교수 유 유 씨.
Thank You.
감사합니다.
Cheers.
건배.
Enjoy the banquet.
연회를 즐겨보세요.
-Allow me to introduce... -No need.
- 소개하자면... - 필요없어요.
Yu You, you don't know
유 당신은 모르죠
he's been wanting to meet you for a long time.
그 사람은 오랫동안 당신을 만나고 싶어했어요.
I've never seen him so crazy about a girl.
나는 그가 여자에게 그렇게 미친 것을 본 적이 없습니다.
You flatter me, Mr Shi.
당신은 나에게 아첨합니다, 미스터 시.
Okay.
좋아요.
We have completed this great task
우리는 이 위대한 임무를 완수했습니다
and I've got a great expert for you.
그리고 당신을 위한 훌륭한 전문가가 있어요.
My dad supports us, that's for sure.
우리 아버지는 우리를 지지해 주십니다. 그건 확실해요.
Next, win the favor of the old people in Yunchuang.
다음으로 운좡 노인들의 환심을 사세요 .
As for your father, do you want...
당신의 아버지에 관해서는 당신이 원하십니까 ...
No need to rush, let's take it slow.
서두르지 말고 천천히 해보자.
Correct.
옳은.
Now we can call ourselves the three minions...
이제 우리는 스스로를 세 명의 하수인이라고 부를 수 있습니다.
I'm not a lackey like you.
나는 당신처럼 부족한 사람이 아닙니다.
Correct. We are like the Jiangcheng Triad,
옳은. 우리는 Jiangcheng Triad 와 같습니다 .
unstoppable with our intelligence.
우리의 지능으로는 막을 수 없습니다.
Cheers.
건배.
Xing Zhou, where are you?
저우싱, 어디야?
(The road is jammed. Give me a little more time.)
(길이 막혔어요. 조금 더 시간을 주세요.)
(I'll be there as soon as possible.)
(최대한 빨리 그곳에 갈게요.)
OK, I'll wait by the side of the road,
알았어, 길가에서 기다릴게
so you don't need to look for me.
그러니 나를 찾을 필요가 없습니다.
Ms. Zheng, long time no see.
Zheng 씨, 오랜만이군요.
What are you doing here?
여기서 뭐하는거야?
Long time no see, Mr Zhang.
오랜만이에요, 장 씨.
I'm here for an interview.
저는 인터뷰를 하러 왔습니다.
I haven't had time to thank you properly
제대로 감사 인사를 전할 시간이 없었어요
for the wonderful article you wrote for me last time.
지난번에 당신이 저를 위해 써준 훌륭한 기사에 대해 .
How about I give you a ride?
내가 당신을 태워주는 게 어때요?
Mr. Zhang, you are too kind.
장 씨, 당신은 너무 친절해요.
You have a lot of experience
경험이 많으시네요
which gives me room to shine.
그것은 나에게 빛날 여지를 준다.
My boyfriend will be here soon.
내 남자친구가 곧 여기에 올 거예요.
No need to trouble you.
당신을 귀찮게 할 필요가 없습니다.
Well, take care of yourself.
글쎄요, 몸 조심하세요.
Miss, are you alone?
아가씨, 혼자예요?
Want me to give you a ride?
태워다 줄까요?
It was raining heavily and it was difficult to get a taxi.
비가 많이 내려 택시를 잡기가 어려웠습니다.
No, thank you. My boyfriend will be here soon.
아니요 괜찮습니다. 내 남자친구가 곧 여기에 올 거예요.
Why are you standing here alone if you have a girlfriend?
여자친구가 있는데 왜 여기 혼자 서 있는 겁니까 ?
Who says having a girlfriend means you can't stand here?
여자친구가 있으면 여기 서 있을 수 없다고 누가 말하던가요?
Why Ms. Zheng is still here?
Zheng 씨는 왜 아직 여기에 있나요?
Didn't you prepare a car for him?
그를 위해 차를 준비하지 않았나요?
He said someone picked him up.
누군가 그를 데리러 왔다고 하더군요.
How much longer, Xing Zhou?
Xing Zhou, 얼마나 더 걸리나요?
I am cold.
차다.
Maybe that person didn't have time?
그 사람은 시간이 없었나 봐요?
Right now, along this road,
지금 이 길을 따라
and heavy rain,
그리고 큰 비,
difficult to get a taxi.
택시 잡기가 어렵다.
Step aside.
비켜서 다.
I know it's raining hard, but I'm waiting for my boyfriend.
비가 많이 오는 건 알지만 남자친구를 기다리고 있어요.
Correct. I have a girlfriend. Thank you and good bye.
옳은. 나는 여자 친구가있다. 감사합니다. 안녕히 계세요.
It can't be him, right?
그 사람일 리가 없지, 그렇지?
Road.
도로.
He was really waiting for his girlfriend.
그는 정말로 여자친구를 기다리고 있었습니다.
I didn't think so
나는 그렇게 생각하지 않았다
he actually has a girlfriend.
그 사람은 사실 여자친구가 있어요.
I spoke to him several times by telephone
나는 그와 전화로 여러 번 이야기를 나눴다.
and I think he's quite easy to get along with.
그리고 내 생각엔 그 사람은 사이좋게 지내기 아주 쉬운 사람인 것 같아.
Maybe because he failed the interview today
아마도 오늘 면접에서 떨어졌기 때문이겠지
and there are people trying to chat with him all day,
그 사람과 하루 종일 대화를 나누려는 사람들도 있고 ,
Plus the weather is very cold,
게다가 날씨도 많이 춥고,
so he was a bit impatient.
그래서 그는 조금 참을성이 없었습니다.
You seem quite worried about whether he has a girlfriend or not.
그 사람에게 여자친구가 있는지 없는지 많이 걱정하는 것 같아요 .
No.
아니요.
I think she is very beautiful,
나는 그녀가 매우 아름답다고 생각한다.
and he is competent at his job.
그리고 그 사람은 자기 일에 능숙해요.
It's natural that he has a girlfriend.
그에게 여자친구가 있는 것은 당연하다.
So, you think she's beautiful
그래서 당신은 그녀가 아름답다고 생각하는가?
and competent in their work?
업무에 능숙합니까?
What we can be certain of is. Internally, they have high expectations
우리가 확신할 수 있는 것은. 내부적으로는 기대가 크다.
if he will pass the position
만약 그 사람이 그 자리를 통과한다면
and got the position of deputy editor.
그리고 부편집장 자리를 얻었습니다.
-Chen Sheng, I noticed something. -What's that?
-Chen Sheng, 뭔가를 발견했습니다. - 그게 뭐죠?
You seem more talented
당신이 더 재능이 있는 것 같아요
become a gossip columnist instead of being my assistant.
내 조수 대신 가십 칼럼니스트가 되어주세요 .
I'm sorry, Shu Yi.
미안해요, 슈이.
Today it is raining heavily and the traffic jam is serious.
오늘은 비가 많이 내리고 교통체증이 심각합니다.
I'm stuck in traffic.
교통이 막혀요.
-You must be cold. -I'm fine.
- 추울 것 같아요. -잘 지내요.
How was your birthday today?
오늘 생일은 어땠나요?
Are you having fun?
당신은 재미?
My boyfriend didn't even celebrate with me. How can I be happy?
내 남자친구는 나와 함께 축하도 하지 않았어요. 어떻게 하면 행복할 수 있나요?
Forgive me.
용서 해줘.
Who is celebrating with you today?
오늘은 누가 당신과 함께 축하하나요 ?
Who else?
그밖에 누가?
Xu Feng?
쉬펑?
He even wears cologne now.
그는 지금도 향수를 뿌린다.
The aroma is light and unique.
향은 가볍고 독특합니다.
The taste is not bad.
맛은 나쁘지 않습니다.
If you meet him again,
그 사람을 다시 만나면,
ask him what cologne he uses.
그에게 어떤 향수를 사용하는지 물어보세요.
I think it suits you too.
내 생각엔 당신에게도 어울리는 것 같아요.
How was the interview today?
오늘 인터뷰는 어땠나요?
Long story.
긴 이야기.
Don't talk about it. Irritating.
그것에 대해 이야기하지 마십시오. 화나게 하는.
Well, don't be mad, honey.
화내지 마세요, 자기야.
Why didn't you answer my call?
왜 내 전화에 응답하지 않았나요?
I'm all yours after work.
퇴근 후에는 나는 모두 당신 것입니다.
No telephones while working.
일하는 동안에는 전화를 할 수 없습니다.
Stop by later.
나중에 들러주세요.
I'll make you long life noodles.
장수 국수 만들어 드릴게요.
It doesn't matter. It is late
그것은 중요하지 않습니다. 늦었 어
and you're not feeling well. Take it easy.
그리고 당신은 몸이 좋지 않습니다. 진정하세요.
There will be many opportunities to make up for it.
그것을 만회할 수 있는 기회가 많이 있을 것입니다 .
Why are you so considerate?
왜 그렇게 사려 깊습니까?
It's because I love you, Stupid.
널 사랑하기 때문이야, 바보야.
It's still your birthday.
아직 생일이잖아
Happy birthday, Xing Zhou.
생일 축하해, 저우싱.
Thank you darling.
고마워요 자기.
I'm going home now.
나는 지금 집에 갈 예정이다.
Hello. What is it?
안녕하세요. 그것은 무엇입니까?
What?
무엇?
I have to tell Mrs. Yi.
이씨 부인에게 말해야 해요.
Where's my phone?
내 전화기는 어디에 있나요?
Hospital?
병원?
How could it be in the hospital?
어떻게 병원에 있을 수 있니?
Was my phone stolen?
내 휴대폰이 도난당했나요?
I was obviously holding my phone when I got into the car.
분명히 차에 탔을 때 나는 휴대폰을 들고 있었습니다 .
What is Xing Zhou doing in the hospital?
Xing Zhou는 병원에서 무엇을 하고 있나요?
Is he sick?
그 사람이 아픈가요?
Did he have a car accident?
그 사람이 교통사고를 당했나요?
He really is here.
그는 정말 여기 있어요.
License plate with repeating numbers.
반복되는 숫자가 있는 번호판.
Better not mess with them.
그들을 건드리지 않는 것이 좋습니다 .
He might be her friend.
그는 그녀의 친구일지도 모릅니다.
Visiting friends in the hospital at night is normal.
밤에 병원에 있는 친구를 방문하는 것은 정상입니다.